

ALINA HUZ

UI/UX Designer

© Ennis, Clare, Ireland (Remote, On-site, Relocation)

& +353 85 202 27 36 ☑ alina.huz.design@gmail.com Bē @alinahuz 🛅 Alina Huz

I am a UI/UX designer whose motivation is to exceed expectations, with over 2 years of experience within the industry. During this time, I gained experience in developing designs for websites in various fields of activity. I approach each project individually. I am set for professional growth with each project, open to gaining new knowledge and mastering new technologies.

Domains in which I worked: Logistics and transport (B2B, B2C), Healthcare, Insurance, E-commerce

I had to work hard to become a UI/UX designer. I have a pharmaceutical education and have been successfully working as a pharmacist for 4 years. But I did not see any prospects for myself in medicine, although I like to take care of people. Now I care about users by studying their behavior and preferences to create the best user experience for them. Therefore, I am very self-motivated and work hard every day for future success.

SKILLS

- · Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD
- · Low/high fidelity Wireframing
- · Responsive and adaptable design
- · Rapid Prototyping, Clickable prototype
- Moodboards
- UI-kits in Figma: components, auto layouts, styles, variations
- Wireframe tools FigJam/Lucid/ Mural/ Wireframe.cc
- · HTML/CSS and basic understanding JS
- · Banners / Animation banners
- · Typographic logo design
- · Strong knowledge of UI/UX principles
- · Planning and conducting user research
- Realisation of personas, user flow maps, prediction of interaction scenarios
- Application of User-centric design methodology
- Knowledge of Nielsen heuristics
- · Understanding the principles of Atomic Design
- · Understanding the principles of Agile/SCRUM
- Teamwork with developers, QA, product manager
- · Full-time availability and time management

CERTIFICATES

"Web designer course" 2019

Educational platform "WayUp" (3 months)

"UX Crash Course: Fundamentals" 2019

Information resource "Medium" (1 month)

"UX from scratch: how to become a UI designer" 2022

Course from Udemy (2 weeks)

"Digital Skills: User Experience" 2022

Course from FutureLearn (3 weeks)

"UX design in Figma. Ux project analytics Ux for web designer" 2022

Course from FutureLearn (2 weeks)

"Code Challenge" 2022

Challenge from CodeInstitute (1 weeks)

LANGUAGE

English - B2 Ukrainian - Native

EXPERIENCE

Freelance / February 2021 - April 2022

Main responsibilities:

- · Communication with clients, briefing, analysis of the received data, implementation of personas, user flow cards, prediction of interaction scenarios, analysis of the target audience and competitors, determination of the goals and objectives of the project;
- · Creation of moodboards and concepts, prototyping and quick sketching;
- · Development of design of landings, banners, multi-page sites, logos;
- · Presentation of your work, preparation of files for layout, collaboration with Frontend developer.

"Delivery group" (Kyiv, Ukraine) Contract / July 2020 - February 2021

Main responsibilities:

- · Communication with clients, briefing, analysis of the received data, analysis of the target audience and competitors, determination of the goals and objectives of the project, development of site architecture, interaction scenarios;
- · Collection of information among employees of the main office of the company, who were also part of the target audience;
- · Development and testing of a prototype;
- · Development of design of multi-page sites, banners, redesign;
- · Presentation of your work directly to the product owner, preparation of files for layout, collaboration with Frontend developer and digital manager.

Web Designer 5 months

Freelance / March 2020 - July 2020

Main responsibilities:

- · Communication with clients, briefing, analysis of the received data, analysis of the target audience and competitors, determination of the goals and objectives of the project;
- · Development of design for landing pages, banners, multi-page sites, redesign;
- · Presentation of your work, preparation of files for layout, collaboration with Frontend developer.

EDUCATION

Limerick and Clare Education and Training Board

English Language, Cambridge B2/ Sept. 2022 - June 2023

Zaporizhzhia State Medical University

Bachelor, Pharmacy/ Sept. 2016 - Jun 2018

Beryslav Medical College

Secondary vocational, Pharmacy/ Sept. 2013 - June 2016